RG 062:007, Town of Berlin
Connecticut State Library
Town of Berlin records
1775-1995
bulk 1775-1884
Connecticut State Library
Berlin (Conn.)
2.75 cubic feet
Tax, election and Borough of Worthington meeting records for the town of Berlin
RG062_007
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Berlin was incorporated in May 1785 and was taken from Farmington, Wethersfield and Middletown. New Britain separated from Berlin in May 1850.
Scope and Content
Tax, election and Borough of Worthington meeting records for the town of Berlin.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Berlin -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Berlin -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Berlin -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Berlin -- Registers; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Berlin
Places:
Berlin (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; Kensington (Conn.)
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1775-1995
  - T000595, 2.5 cubic feet
    - Registry lists/lists of electors, 1775-1850, 1884 (Box 1)
    - Borough of Worthington meeting minutes, 1834-1846 (Box 2)
    - Rate book, 1883 (Box 2)
    - Kensington tax abstracts, 1818, 1822, 1840, 1841, 1842, 1844, 1845, 1846, 1847, 1848 (Box 3)
      scattered
    - Worthington tax abstracts, 1822-1849 (Box 4)
  - 2015-022, .25 cubic feet
    - Berlin Junior High School Ground Survey and Photo Expedition by John Kaestle, McGee School, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
    - Conceptual Improvement Plan, Project: Proposed Circuit City, Newington, Connecticut, Proponent: Circuit City Stores, Inc., Richmond, Virginia, 1994-1995; 1 sheet; 1:40 (Box 1)
    - Proposed Zone Change For Lots 1, 8 and 8A Block 121, Wilbur Cross Highway, Berlin – Conn., Engineering Department, Town of Berlin, Berlin, Connecticut, 1995 May 19; 1 sheet; 1:100 (Box 1)
    - Site Development Plan for Circuit City located in Newington, Connecticut, 1994-1995; 13 sheets; 1:40 (Box 1)